const questionBank = [
  {
    question : "What are the names of the Minions in the 2015 film minion?",
    ans : "Kevin, Bob and Stuart",
    options :[ "Kevin, Bob and Stuart",
               "Kevin, Bob and Nathan",
               "Kevin, Sally and Stuart",
               "Gareth, Bob and Stuart"]
  },
  
  {
    question : "Who is the big sister in The Despicable Me Films?",
    ans : "Margo",
    options:["Edith",
             "Margo",
             "Agnus",
             "Heather"]
  },
  
  {
    question : "What was the first thing Gru ever stole?",
    ans : "The Queens Crown",
    options : ["The Queens Crown",
               "The Moon",
               "His Lunch",
               "The Pyramid"]
  },
  {
    question : "Why did the Minions go to Orlando?",
    ans : "Villain Con",
    options : ["Vacation",
               "Villain Con",
               "To find Gru",
               "To find some bananas"]
  },
  {
    question : "How did all the minions arrive in London?",
    ans : "The tube",
    options : ["A boat",
               "The tube",
               "An airplane",
               "Swam"]
  },
  
  {
    question : "What is the minions favourite food?",
    ans : "Bananas",
    options : ["Banannnas",
               "Bannnnnanas",
               "Banans",
               "Bananas"]
  },
  
  {
    question : "Who made the purple minions?",
    ans : "El Macho",
    options : ["Dr Nefario",
               "Gareth",
               "Gru",
               "El Macho"]
  },
  {
    question : "What is the purpose of the purple minions?",
    ans : "Be his henchmen",
    options : ["Take care of everyone",
               "Love the minions",
               "Be his henchmen",
               "Blow up the world"]
  },
  
  {
    question : "What is the name of the Minion Ride in Universal Studios?",
    ans : "Minion Mayhem",
    options : ["Margo madness",
               "Unicorn Alley",
               "Minion Twerking",
               "Minion Mayhem"]
  },
  {
    question : "Minions speak a mixture of ....?",
    ans : "Spanish, English, French, and Italian, with additional elements of Russian and Korean",
    options : ["additional elements of Russian and Korean",
               "Spanish, English, French, and Italian, with additional elements of Russian and Korean",
               "Spanish, with additional elements of Russian and Korean",
               "Spanish, English, French"]
  }
  
  ];